在左边有一个很棒的时刻
There's a great moment over here on the left side
上面写着，“伟大的巴林顿。”
where it says, "Great Barrington."
而O有一个平方。
And the O has a squareness to it.
这很让人兴奋，但同样有趣
That's exciting to see here, but then equally fun
在接下来的几页中，
in subsequent pages,
在这张地图上有两条街道，
there are a pair of streets in this one map,
哈伯德街和查尔斯街。
Hubbard Street and Charles Street.
而哈伯德，在U的底部有一条很浅的曲线，
And Hubbard, the bottom of the U has this very shallow curve,
但是下面的查尔斯街有一个非常圆的c。
but then Charles Street below it has a very rounded C.
所以，我觉得这个设计师在挣扎
So, I feel like this designer is struggling
有很多同样的想法可以解决。
with a lot of these same ideas that can be resolved.